Guide to the James O. Brown Associates Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Author File
  - Plamenatz, John Petrov (Box 297)
  - Platis, George G. (Box 297)
  - Platt, Bernice K. (Box 297)
  - Plimpton, Sarah (Box 297)
  - Poillon, Katharine 8c Charlotte, & Alexander Gardiner (Box 297)
  - Pollard, Joseph Percival (Box 297)
  - Pompian, Rita (Box 297)
  - Pond, Seymour G. (Box 297)
  - Ponsonby, D.A. (Box 297)
    (See: Rybot, Doris A)
  - Poole, Frederick King (Box 297)
  - Pope-Hennessy, James (Box 297)
  - Pope-Hennessy, Dame Una Birch (Box 297)
  - Poppino, Kathryn (Box 297)
  - Porter, Alyene (Box 297)
  - Porter, Joyce (Box 297)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne (Box 297)
  - Porter, Russell B. (Box 297)
  - Porter, Verne (Box 297)
  - Porterfield, Robert (Box 297)
  - Porzak, Brian (Box 297)
  - Post, Melville Davisson (Box 298)
  - Postle, Denis (Box 298)
  - Potter, Daniel (Box 298)
  - Powell, Dawn (Box 298)
  - Powell, Gordon (Box 298)
  - Powell, John Benjamin (Box 298)
  - Power-Waters, Alma (Box 298)
  - Powers, Anne (Anne Powers Schwartz) (Box 298)
  - Powers, James T. (Box 298)
  - Powers, John R. (Box 298)
  - Powers, Marcella (Box 298)
  - Powers, Richie (Box 298)
  - Powys, John Cowper (Box 298)
  - Powys, Llewelyn (Box 298)
  - Poynter, Nelson (Box 298)
  - Pratt, Agnes Edwards Pothery (Box 298)
    ("Agnes Rothery")
  - Pratt, Charles (Box 298)
  - Pratt, Joseph Gaither (Box 298)
  - Pratt, Ruth Sears Baker (Mrs. John T.) (Box 298)
  - Prebble, John Edward Curtis (Box 299)
  - Prescott, Allen (Box 299)
  - Pribe, Walter A. (Box 299)
  - Price, Burr (Box 299)
  - Price, H. Bruce (Box 299)
  - Price, James F. (Box 299)
    ("Jungle Jim")
  - Prince, Morton P. (Box 299)
  - Pringle, Henry F. (Box 299)
  - Proctor, Kay (Box 299)
  - Prosser, William (Box 299)
  - Protter, Eric (Box 299)
  - Pruner, Leonora (Box 299)
  - Pugh, Marshall (Box 299)
  - Pullar, Philippa (Box 299)
  - Pulleyn, John J. (Box 299)
  - Purdon, Eric (Box 299)
  - Purdue, Howell & Elizabeth (Box 299)
  - Purdy, Andrew James (Box 299)
  - Purdy, James (Box 299)
  - Purser, Philip (Box 299)
  - Purvis, Melvin H., Jr. (Box 299)
  - Putnam, Clay (Box 300)
  - Putnam, George Palmer (Box 300)
  - Putnam, Peter Brock (Box 300)
  - Pye, Michael & Linda Myles (Box 301)
  - Pyke, Magnus (Box 301)
  - Pynchon, George M. & Alfred S. Lilly (Box 301)
  - Quennell, Peter (Box 301)
  - Quentin, Dorothy (Box 301)
  - Quilici, Folco (Box 301)
  - Quigley, Martin, Jr. (Box 301)
  - Rachleff, Oven S. (Box 302)
  - Rachlin, Nahid (Box 302)
  - Rader, Barbara (Box 302)
  - Räikkönen, Erkki (Box 302)
  - Railey, Hilton Howell (Box 302)
  - Raitt, Alan W. (Box 302)
  - Ramage, Mary (Box 302)
  - Ramsaye, Terry (Box 302)
  - Rand, Sally (Box 302)
  - Randall, Russell Edward (Box 302)
  - Randolph, June (Box 302)
  - Random, Reginald (Richard L. Brooks) (Box 302)
  - Raphael, David Daiches (Box 302)
  - Rascoe, Burton (Box 302)
  - Rasponi, Lanfranco, Count (Box 302)
  - Rauch, Constance (Box 303)
  - Rauch, Earl M., Jr. (Box 303)
  - Ravage, Marcus Eli (Box 303)
  - Raven, Simon Arthur Noel (Box 303)
  - Ravin, Neil (Box 303)
  - Ray, Elizabeth (Box 303)
  - Raymer, Paul H,, Jr. (Box 303)
  - Raymond, Ann (Ann Raymond Wood) (Box 303)
  - Raymond, E. Neill (Box 303)
  - Read, Arthur C. (Box 303)
  - Read, Harlan Eugene (Box 303)
  - Read, Jan (Box 303)
  - Ready, John J. (Box 303)
  - RedMay ne, John (Herbert Wood & Juliet Piggott Wood) (Box 303)
  - Redner, Joseph J. (Box 303)
  - Reed, George (Box 303)
  - Reed, Joel M. (Box 303)
  - Reed, Tom (Box 303)
  - Rees, Jean A. (Box 303)
  - Reese, Henry A. (Box 303)
  - Reese, Terence (John Terence Reese) (Box 303)
  - Reeves, Bruce D. (Box 303)
  - Regan, Kate Watts (Box 304)
  - Reichenbach, Harry & David Freedman (Box 304)
  - Reid, James Macarthur (Box 304)
  - Reid, Robert W. (Box 304)
  - Reilly, Henry Joseph (Box 304)
  - Reilly, Patricia (Box 304)
  - Reilly, Robin & George Savage (Box 304)
  - Reily, E. Mont. (Box 304)
  - Reinhardt, Günther P. (Box 304)
  - Reinhart, Robert C. (Box 304)
  - Reiss, Robert (Box 304)
  - Reiter, Charles Jules (Box 304)
  - Renaud, Ralph Edward (Box 304)
  - Renault, Mary (Mary Challans) (Box 304-305)
  - Renon, Erika (Erika Renon von Mohrenschildt) (Box 306)
  - Renshaw, Patrick (Box 306)
  - Renslow, Alphine (Alphine Billett) (Box 306)
  - Reppy, Alison & Albert P. Blaustein (Box 306)
  - Reston, James Barrett (Box 306)
  - Revel, Harry (Box 306)
  - Reyher, Ferdinand (Box 306)
  - Reynolds, David C. (Box 306)
  - Reynolds, Patricia (Box 306)
  - Reynolds, Quentin (Box 306)
  - Reynolds, R. Bruce (Box 306)
  - Reynolds, Reginald (Box 306)
  - Rhoads, Geraldine (Box 306)
  - Rhodes, Evan (Box 306)
  - Rhodes, Lucille (Box 306)
  - Rhodes, Richard L. (Box 307)
  - Riad, Mahmoud (Box 307)
  - Ribble, Margaret (Box 307)
  - Ricci, Barbara (Barbara J Guignon) (Box 307)
  - Rice, Charles O. (Box 307)
  - Rice, Edward, Jr. (Box 307)
  - Rice, Edward, III (Box 307)
  - Rice, Harry C. (Box 307)
  - Rice, William (Box 307)
  - Rice, William H. (Box 307)
  - Richards, Alun (Box 307)
  - Richards, Brian (Box 307)
  - Richardson, Mrs. Frank D. (Box 307)
  - Richardson, Joanna (Box 307)
  - Richardson, Rosamond (Box 307)
  - Richardson, Tracy (Box 307)
  - Richmond, Dick (Box 307)
  - Ridenour, Ruth (Box 307)
  - Rider, Anne (Anne Driver) (Box 307)
  - Ridley, Jasper (Box 308)
  - Ridpath, Ian (Box 308)
  - Riencourt, Amaury, Marquis de (Box 308)
  - Riesenberg, Felix (Box 308)
  - Rifkin, Shepard (Box 308)
  - Riis, Roger William (Box 308)
  - Riley, Paula (Box 308)
  - Rimington, Critchell (Box 308)
  - Riordan, Lee (Box 308)
  - Ritner, Peter (Box 308)
  - River, W.L. (Les River) (Box 308)
  - Robb, Walter (Box 308)
  - Robbins, Chris (Box 308)
  - Robbins, June & Jhan (Box 309)
  - Robbins, Keith Gilbert (Box 309)
  - Robert, Derek (Box 309)
  - Roberts, Dorothy James (Box 309)
  - Roberts, Edward F. (Box 309)
  - Roberts, Henry W. & Ouida Roberts (Box 309)
  - Roberts, John Hawley (Box 310)
  - Roberts, Nesta (Box 310)
  - Roberts, Sheila (Box 310)
  - Roberts, William Holloway (Box 310)
  - Robeson, Kenneth CPaul Ernst 1 (Box 310)
  - Robey, Claire (Box 310)
  - Robins, Denise (Box 310)
  - Robinson, Anthony (Box 310)
  - Robinson, Robert Henry (Box 310)
  - Robinson, Sheila (Box 310)
    ("Sheila Radley", "Hester Rowan")
  - Robinson, Sondra Till (Box 310)
  - Robson, James (Box 310)
  - Roby, Kinley E. (Box 311)
  - Roby, Mary Linn (Box 311)
    ("Pamela D'Arcy", "Roberta Fuller", "Shirley McKinney", "Mary Wilson")
  - Roche, Lise (Lise Roche Bragg) (Box 311)
  - Rodger, Sarah-Elizabeth (Box 311)
  - Rodgers, Cleveland (Box 311)
  - Rodney, George B. (Box 311)
  - Rogers, Lela E. (Box 311)
  - Rogers, Maggie D. (Box 311)
  - Rogers, M. Robert (Box 311)
  - Rogers, William Garland (Box 311)
  - Rogow, Arnold A. (Box 311-312)
  - Rohan, Donald (Box 312)
  - Rolland, Susie (Box 312)
  - Rollo, Naomi June (Edith Alice Naomi June Bug Allen Solum Rollo), "Ed Allen", "Edith Jay" (Box 312)
  - Rolo, Charles J. (Box 312)
  - Rom, M. Martin (Box 312)
  - Romaine, Octave (Box 312)
  - Ronalds, Mary Teresa (Box 312)
    ("Teresa Sheridan", "Mary Waddingham")
  - Roose-Evans, James (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Andre & Heide (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor B. Alexander (Mrs. Theodore) (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Elliott (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, G. Hall (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, Grace Stackpole Lockwood (Mrs. A.B.) (Box 313)
  - Roosevelt, James (Box 313)
  - Roper, Lester V., Jr. (Box 313)
    ("Samantha Lester")
  - Rose, Billy (Box 314)
  - Rose, Philip Sheridan (Box 314)
  - Rosemeyer, Nita (Box 314)
  - Rosenbauer, Marguerite Coyle (Box 314)
  - Rosenberg, Anna M (Box 314)
  - Rosenberg, Jerry M (Box 314)
  - Rosenblum, Robert (Box 314)
  - Rosendahl, Charles E (Box 314)
  - Rosenman, Dorothy Reuben (Box 314)
  - Rosenman, Samuel Irving (Box 314)
  - Rosenstiel, Louise Johnson (Box 314)
  - Rosetahl, David Cecil (Box 314)
  - Rosmond, Babette (Box 314)
    ("Francis N. Arroway", "Rosamond Campion")
  - Rosner, Joseph (Box 314)
  - Ross, Betty (Box 314)
  - Ross, Ishbel (Box 314)
  - Ross, Jessica (Box 314)
  - Ross, Lanny (Box 314)
  - Rossant, M.J. (Box 314)
  - Rote, Al (Box 315)
  - Roth, Arthur "Slater McGurk", "Barney Mara", "Pete Pomeroy" (Box 315)
  - Roth, Hal (Box 315)
  - Rothenstein, Sir John Knevstub Maurice (Box 315)
  - Rothstein, Carolyn (Mrs. Arnold) (Box 315)
  - Roussy de Sales, Count Aymon de (Box 315)
  - Roussy de Sales, Raine Tracy, Countess Raoul de (Box 315)
  - Rover, Constance (Box 315)
  - Roves, Barbara (Box 316)
  - Rowland, Henry Cottrell (Box 316)
  - Rowland, John T. (Box 316)
  - Rowley, Peter (Box 316)
  - Royce, Kenneth (Box 316)
  - Rozin, Skip (Louis E. Rozin) (Box 316-317)
  - Rubens, Doris (Box 317)
  - Rudofsky, Bernard (Box 317)
  - Ruesch, Hans (Box 317)
  - Ruffini, Eugene & Francis A.J. Ianni (Box 317)
  - Ruhm, Herbert (Box 317)
  - Rukeyser, Merryle Stanley (Box 317)
  - Rummell, Frances V. (Box 317)
  - Runyon, Damon (Box 317)
  - Rushmore, Robert (Box 317)
  - Rushworth, Emily C. (Box 317)
  - Russcol, Herbert (Box 317)
  - Russell, Donna (Box 318)
    ("Serene Grey")
  - Russell, Dora Winifred Black, Countess Russell (Box 318)
  - Russell, Franklin (Box 318)
  - Russell, Isabel R. (Box 318)
  - Russell, Peter (Box 318)
  - Russell, Phillips (Box 318)
  - Russell, Ray (Box 318)
  - Rust, Gordon A. (Box 318)
    ("Denys Ives")
  - Rutenber, Ralph (Box 319)
  - Rutherford, Douglas (Box 319)
  - Rutledge, Nancy (Box 319)
  - Ryan, John Fergus (Box 319)
  - Ryan, John T. (Box 319)
  - Rybot, Doris (Box 319)
    ("D.A. Ponsonby", "Sarah Tempest")
  - Ryder, Ellen (Box 319)
  - Ryder, Steve (Box 319)
  - Sabatini, Len (Box 320)
  - Sabbag, Robert & Charles Forsman (Box 320)
  - Sabin, Francene & Louis (Box 320)
  - Sachs, Emanie Nahm (Emanie Nahm Arling) (Box 320)
  - Sachs, Judith (Box 320)
    ("Jesse Howland")
  - Sackville-West, Vita (Box 320)
  - Sager, Gordon (Box 321)
  - Said, Kurban, Jenia Graman, & Lucy F. Tal (Box 321)
  - St. Clair, David (Box 321-322)
  - St. Julien, Raymond A. (Box 322)
  - Sakier, Rebecca (Box 322)
  - Sale, David (Box 322)
  - Sales, Grover & Georgia MacLeod Sales (Box 322-323)
  - Salomon, Alice (Box 323)
  - Salvato, Sharon Anne & Cornelia M. Parkinson (Box 323)
    ("Day Taylor")
  - Sanborn, Orville C. (Box 324)
  - Sanders, Marion K. (Box 324)
  - Sanders, Pamela (Box 324)
  - Sandys, Elspeth (Box 324)
  - Santa Cruz, Lucia (Box 324)
  - Sapin, Ruth (Ruth Sapin Hurwitz) (Box 324)
  - Sapinsley, Barbara (Box 324)
  - Saporiti, Piero (Box 324)
  - Sarasas, Phra (Box 324)
  - Sarasvati, Swami (Box 324)
  - Sarban (Box 324)
  - Sass, Herbert Ravenel (Box 325)
  - Saul, John Ralston (Box 325)
  - Saunders, Carole G.O. (.Carole G.O. Finnegan) (Box 325)
  - Saunders, Jean (Box 325)
    ("Jean Innes", "Rowena Summers")
  - Savell, Morton (Box 325)
  - Saxton, Alexander P. (Box 325)
  - Scanlon, Robert Howard (Box 325)
  - Scarrone, Louis A. (Box 325)
  - Scheff, Fritzi (Box 325)
  - Schell, Merle (Box 325)
  - Schellie, Don (Box 325)
  - Schiller, Babette (Box 325)
  - Schloss, Irvin E. (Box 325)
  - Schmidt, James Norman (Box 326)
    ("James Norman")
  - Schneck, Stephen (Box 326)
  - Schonfeld, Robert D, & Peter McCabe (Box 326)
  - Schonning, Gunnar (Box 326)
  - Schriver, Jacquelyn Boyd (Box 326)
  - Schroeder, Mary (Box 326)
  - Schultz, Alan Brener (Box 326)
  - Schultz, John (Box 326)
  - Schultz, Sigrid (Box 326)
  - Schurr, Cathleen (Box 326)
  - Schurz, William Lytle (Box 326)
  - Schwab, Laurence, Jr. (Box 327)
  - Schwalberg, Carol (Box 327-328)
  - Schwartz, Norman (Box 328)
  - Scobey, Joan (Box 328)
  - Scolnick, Sylvan (Box 328)
  - Scott, Evelyn D. (Mrs. John Metcalfe) (Box 329)
  - Scott, John (Box 329)
  - Scott, Tom & Geoffrey Cousins (Box 329)
  - Scott, V.E. (Box 329)
  - Scott, Warwick (Box 329)
  - Scully, Frank (Box 329)
  - Seabrook, William Beuhler (Box 329)
  - Seabury, David & Florence Guy Seabury (Box 329)
  - Seadler, Silas F. (Box 329)
  - Sears, Joseph Hamblen (Box 329)
  - Sedgwick, Ruth Woodbury (Box 329)
  - Seebach, Julius F., Jr. (Box 329)
  - Segal, Albert (Box 329)
  - Segal, Joyce (Box 329)
  - Selby, John Allen (Box 329-330)
  - Selendy, Janine M. & Ogden R. Reid (Box 330)
  - Seligman, Ben B. (Box 330)
  - Service, Alastair Stanley Douglas (Box 330)
  - Sevareid, Eric (Box 330)
  - Seymour, Miranda (Box 330)
  - Shaara, Michael (Box 331)
  - Shadbolt, Maurice (Box 331)
  - Shafer, Chet (Box 331)
  - Shane, Ted (Box 331)
  - Shannon, Robert Terry (Box 331)
  - Shapiro, Fred C. (Box 331)
  - Shapiro, Harry Lionel (Box 331)
  - Shapiro, Jim (Box 332)
  - Sharman, Miriam (Box 332)
  - Sharpe, Thomas Ridley (Box 332)
  - Shaw, Marian (Marian Shaw Lipschutz) (Box 332)
  - Shaw, Percy (Box 332)
  - Shead, Ann (Box 332)
  - Sheffield, Margaret (Box 332)
  - Shelby, Graham (Box 332)
    ("James Gant")
  - Sheldon, Deyan (Diane Sheldon, Deann Sheldon) (Box 332)
  - Sheratsky, Rodney E. (Box 333)
  - Sherman, Ray- (Box 333)
  - Sherman, Robert Charles (Box 333)
  - Sherriff, Robert Cedric (Box 333)
  - Sherrill, Robert (Box 333)
  - Sherry, Sylvia (Box 333)
  - Shestack, Melvin B. (Box 333)
  - Shields, Clydene H. (Box 334)
    ("Clydene Hoke")
  - Shippey, Lee (Box 334)
  - Shipway, George M. (Box 334)
  - Shirley, Sylvia (Box 334)
  - Shore, Wilma (Box 334)
  - Shorris, Earl (Box 334)
  - Shreve, Carl (Box 334)
  - Shubert, Lee (Box 334)
  - Shubert, Lynn (Box 334)
  - Shulman, Sondra (Box 334)
  - Shultz, Gladys Denny (Box 334-335)
  - Shultz, Henry (Box 335)
  - Sidore, May B. (Box 336)
  - Silen, B.H. (Box 336)
    ("H.B. Niles")
  - Sill, Louise Morgan (Box 336)
  - Silva, Julian (Box 336)
  - Silver, A.B. (Box 336)
  - Silver, Nathan (Box 336)
  - Simmons, Addison (Box 336)
  - Simmons, Ernest J. (Box 336)
  - Simons, Orrin (Box 336)
  - Simpkin, Richard E. (Box 336)
  - Simpson, Colin (Box 336)
  - Simpson, Jeffrey (Box 336)
  - Simpson, N.F. (Box 336)
  - Sims, George (Box 336)
  - Sinclair, John Franklin (Box 336)
  - Sinclair, May (Box 336)
  - Sircom, Arthur (Box 336)
  - Sisson, Rosemary Anne (Box 336)
  - Sjogren, Eric (Box 336)
  - Skattebol, Lars (Box 337)
  - Skinner, Henrietta Charming Dana (Box 337)
  - Skinner, Richard Dana (Box 337)
  - Sklar, Robert (Box 337)
  - Skrainka, Philip (Box 337)
  - Slattery, Charles V. (Box 337)
  - Sloat, Marcia Gwynne (Box 337)
  - Slocum, William J. (Box 337)
  - Slosberg, Bertha (Box 337)
  - Smalley, Peter (Box 337)
  - Smallzried, Kathleen Ann (Box 337)
    ("Guy Howard Hansen III")
  - Smith, Alfred Emanuel (Box 337)
  - Smith, Alvin (Box 337)
  - Smith, Anthony John Francis (Box 337)
  - Smith, Bradley (Box 337)
  - Smith, Carleton (Box 337)
  - Smith, Constance (Box 337)
  - Smith, Dick (Box 337)
  - Smith, E. Yale (Box 337)
  - Smith, Edward Ellis (Box 337)
  - Smith, Edward H. (Box 337)
  - Smith, Mrs. E. [fl. 1720] (Box 337)
  - Smith, Emma (Box 337)
  - Smith, Godfrey (Box 338)
  - Smith, Henry Justin (Box 338)
  - Smith, Hal (Box 338)
  - Smith, Holland McTyeire (Box 338)
  - Smith, Howard E., Jr. (Box 338)
  - Smith, Julian (Box 339)
  - Smith, Margarita (Box 339)
  - Smith, Nicol (Box 339)
  - Smith, Richard (Box 339)
  - Smith, Richard C. (Box 339)
  - Smith, Robert B. (Box 339)
  - Smith, Roger H. (Box 339)
  - Smith, Vian (Box 339)
  - Snow, Charles Percy, Baron Snow (Box 339)
  - Sobel, Bernard (Box 339)
  - Sochurek, Howard (Box 339)
  - Sokoloff, Alice Hunt (Box 339)
  - Solomon, Leo M. (Box 339)
  - Somerville, A.W. & Virginia Leddy Somerville (Box 340)
  - Sonnenberg, Benjamin (Box 340)
  - Sorel, Marilyn (Box 340)
  - Spach, John Thorn (Box 340)
  - Spademan, William Mode (Box 340)
  - Sparkes, Boyden (Box 340)
  - Speicher, John (Box 340)
  - Spences, Colin (Box 340)
  - Sper, Norman L (Box 340)
  - Spielberger, Charles (Box 340)
  - Spieler, F. Joseph (Box 340)
  - Spivack, Kathleen (Box 340)
  - Spolansky, Jacob (Box 341)
  - Spotts, Dean (Box 341)
  - Springs, Elliott White (Box 341)
  - Spurling, Hilary (Box 341)
  - Stacey, Nicholas (Box 341)
  - Stacey, Tom (.Thomas C.G. Stacey) (Box 341)
  - Stafford, Jean (Box 341-344)
  - Stafford, Marie Ahnighito Peary (Box 344)
  - Stafford-Clark, David (Box 344)
  - Stallings, Laurence (Box 344)
  - Stanfill, Francesca (Box 344)
  - Stanley-Wrench, Margaret (Box 344)
  - Stanton, Will (Box 344)
  - Stare, Frederick J. (Box 344)
  - Stark, Jean (Box 344)
  - Starr, Jonathan (Box 344)
  - Stavis, Barrie (Box 344)
  - Stechan, H.O. (Box 344)
  - Steele, Wilbur Daniel (Box 344)
  - Stein, Benjamin J. (Box 345)
  - Stein, Sol (Box 345)
  - Steinberg, Alfred (Box 345)
  - Stephens, Martha (Box 345)
  - Stephenson, Hugh (Box 345)
  - Stern, Laurence (Box 345)
  - Stevens, Henry Bailey (Box 345)
  - Stevenson, Archibald Eving (Box 345)
  - Stevenson, Dorothy Emily (Mrs. John R. Peploe) (Box 345)
  - Stevenson, Joanne (Box 345)
  - Stewart, Ada J. (Box 345)
  - Stewart, Mary Florence Elionor Rainbow (Box 345)
  - Stewart, William C. (Box 345)
  - Stiles, Lela (Box 345)
  - Stilwell, Joseph W. & Winifred A. (Box 345)
  - Stinchcomb, F. Philip (Box 346)
  - Stirling, Yates, Jr. (Box 346)
  - Stone, Isidor Feinstein (Box 346)
  - Storrs, William W. (Box 346)
  - Stott, R.E. (Box 346)
  - Strakosch, Avery (Box 346)
  - Strange, Lily (Mrs. William L.) (Box 346)
  - Straub, Bernard (Box 346)
  - Straus, Dorothea Liebmann (Box 346)
  - Stream, Arnold C (Box 347)
  - Strickland, Verne (Box 347)
  - Strode, Hudson (Box 347)
  - Stuart, Ian (Box 347)
  - Stuhldreher, Harry (Box 347)
  - Sturges-Jones, Marion (Mrs. Ralph W. Wescott) (Box 347)
  - Sturhahn, Lawrence (Box 347)
  - Sturm, Alexander McCormick (Box 347)
  - Styles, Showell (Box 347)
  - Sullivan Ed (Box 347)
  - Sullivan, Frank (Box 347)
  - Sullivan, Sheila (Box 347)
  - Sully, Kathleen (Box 347)
  - Sulzberger, Cyrus Leo (Box 347)
  - Summer, Dick (Box 347)
  - Summersby, Kay (Kathleen McCarthy-Morrogh Summersby Morgan) (Box 347)
  - Summerton, Margaret Ethel (Box 347)
    ("Jan Roffman")
  - Sumner, Gee Lynn (Box 347)
  - Sumner, Richard William (Box 347)
  - Sun, Gus (Box 347)
  - Sutherland, Herbert Warren (Box 347)
  - Sutton, George W. & Harold E. Hartney (Box 347)
  - Sutton, Larry (Box 347)
  - Sutton, Lee (Box 347)
  - Sutton, Stack (Maurice Lewis Sutton) (Box 347)
  - Swados, Harvey (Box 348-349)
  - Swanson, Harold Norling (Box 350)
  - Swanson, Olga (Box 350)
  - Sweeney, Christopher (Box 350)
  - Sweenry, Walter Campbell (Box 350)
  - Sweeny, Charles (Box 350)
  - Sweet, A, Porter S (Box 350)
  - Sweetland, Reginald (Box 350)
  - Sykes, Gerald (Box 350)
  - Symons, Geraldine (Dorothy G. Symons) (Box 350)
  - Symons, Julian Gustave (Box 350)
  - Tabouis, Geneviève (Box 350)
  - Tallent, Norman (Box 350)
  - Talton, Reedy (Box 350)
  - Tambimuttu, Meary James Thurairajah (Box 350)
  - Tarassuk, Leonid (Box 351)
  - Tarleton, Fiswoode (Box 351)
  - Tarrant, John J. (Box 351)
  - Tauber, Peter (Box 351)
  - Taubman, Howard (Box 351)
  - Tayar, Graham (Box 352)
  - Taylor, Deems (Box 352)
  - Taylor, F. Chase (Box 352)
    ("Colonel Lemuel Q. Stoopnagle")
  - Taylor, Geoff (Box 352)
  - Taylor, Harris (Box 352)
  - Taylor, John Gerald (Box 352)
  - Taylor, Loren (Box 352)
  - Taylor, Robert Lewis (Box 352)
  - Telscombe, Anne (Marie Joan Catton Dobbs) (Box 352)
  - Telushkin, Joseph & Dennis Prager (Box 352)
  - Temko, Allan (Box 353)
  - Temperley, Howard Reed (Box 353)
  - Temple, Mildred (Box 353)
  - Temple, Philip (Box 353)
  - Temple, Shirley (Box 353)
  - Templeton, Charles (Box 353)
  - Ten Eyck, James (Box 353)
  - Terrall, Robert (Box 353)
  - Terrell, St. John (Box 353)
  - Terry, Howard L. (Box 353)
  - Tetlow, Edwin (Box 353)
  - Thayer, James Stewart (Box 354)
  - Thane, Elswyth (Elswyth Thane Beebe) (Box 354)
  - Thesiger, Wilfred (Box 354)
  - Thorn, Robert (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Craig (Box 354)
    ("David Grant", "David Owen")
  - Thomas, Ethel L, Dodd (Mrs. A.E.) (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Hugh Swynnerton (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Lowell (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Peter (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Rowland (Box 354)
  - Thomas, Ruth (Box 354)
  - Thompson, Anne Armstrong (Box 355)
  - Thompson, Brian (Box 356)
  - Thompson, Cecil Vincent Raymond (Box 356)
  - Thompson, George Selden "Terry Andrews", "George Selden" & Kenneth Heuer (Box 356)
  - Thompson, Jay (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Jim (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Jo Ann S. (Box 357)
  - Thompson, John M. (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Kate (Kathleen Alice Thompson) (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Kenneth (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Sir Robert Grainger Ker (Box 357)
  - Thompson, T.B. (Box 357)
  - Thompson, Vivian L. (Box 357-358)
  - Thompson, William Crawford (Box 358)
  - Thomson, A.W.S. (Sandy Thomson) (Box 358)
  - Thorburn, Donaldson & Lois Long (Box 358)
  - Thorgersen, Ed (Box 358)
  - Thorne, Ann (Box 358)
  - Thorne, Ennis P. (Box 358)
  - Thorpe, Edward (Box 358)
  - Thurber, Jane B. (Box 358)
  - Tighe, Eileen (Box 358)
  - Tindall, Gillian Elizabeth (Box 358)
  - Tinnin, David Bruce (Box 359)
  - Tisdale, Frederick S. (Box 360)
  - Tobenkin, Elias (Box 360)
  - Tobey, Robert A. (Box 360)
  - Todd, Ian Menzies (Box 360)
  - Todd, Michael, Jr. (Box 360)
  - Tolstoy, Alexandra & The Tolstoy Foundation, Inc. (Box 360)
  - Tomaino, Michael (Box 360)
  - Tompkins, Warwick M. (Box 360)
  - Toms, Laraine (Box 360)
  - Tonks, Rosemary (Box 360)
  - Toogood, Granville E. (Thomas Granville) (Box 360)
  - Tooker, Dan & Roger Hofheins (Box 360)
  - Tootle, Harry King (Box 360)
  - Tornato, Renato & Joel M. Reed (Box 360)
  - Torr, Dominic (John Pedler) (Box 360)
  - Torrance, Arthur Frederick (Box 360)
  - Torrey, Alice (Box 360)
  - Totten, Ralph J. (Box 360)
  - Townsend, Irving (Box 360)
  - Tracy, Honor (Box 360)
  - Trafford, Jeremy (Box 360)
  - Trahey, Jane (Box 361)
  - Traube, Shepard (Box 361)
  - Treadwell, Sophie (Box 361)
  - Treat, Roger (Box 361)
  - Trego, Frank H (Box 361)
  - Trevelyan, Humphrey, Baron Trevelyan (Box 361)
  - Triandis, Harry C. & James H. Davis (Box 361)
  - Trimmer, Eric James (Box 361)
  - Trotsky, Leon (Box 361)
  - Trouncer, Margaret Lahey (Box 361)
  - Tucker, Helen (Box 362-363)
  - Tucker, Pat T. "Tommy" (Box 363)
  - Tudor, Charles William Matthews (Box 363)
  - Tufnell, Nicholas (Box 363)
  - Tuller, Walter K. (Box 363)
  - Tully, Grace G. (Box 363)
  - Tully, Jim (Box 363)
  - Tunis, John R. (Box 363)
  - Tunney, Gene (James Joseph Tunney) (Box 363)
  - Tuohy, Frank (Box 363)
  - Turnbaugh, Douglas Blair (Box 363)
  - Turner, Ernest Sackville (Box 363)
  - Turner, Florence Hayes (Box 363)
  - Turner, Frederick (Box 363)
  - Turner, Kay E (Box 363)
  - Turner, Timothy G. (Box 363)
  - Turton, Carol Hillinger (Carol Hollinger) • (Box 364)
  - Tusiani, Joseph (Box 364)
  - Tuttle, Margaretta Muhlenberg (Box 364)
  - Twomey, Katherine (Box 364)
  - Tygiel, Jules (Box 364)
  - Tylden-Wright, David (Box 364)
  - Tyler, Mary (Box 364)
  - Tynan, Kenneth Peacock (Box 364)
  - Ubina, Joy W. (Box 364)
  - Ulasi, Adaora Lily (Box 364)
  - Ulio, James A. (Box 364)
  - Underwood, John (Box 364)
  - Unruh, Fritz von (Box 364)
  - Urquhart, Brian Edward (Box 365)
  - Vandegrift, Beatrice Ashton (Box 365)
  - Vandegrift, Katharine (Box 365)
  - Vandenberg, Hazel H, Whittaker (Mrs. Arthur H.) (Box 365)
  - Vanderbilt, Amy (Box 365)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, Jr. (Box 365)
  - Van Deusen, John G. (Box 365)
  - Van Duzen, Barbara (Box 365)
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem (Box 365)
  - Van Rensselaer, Philip (Box 365)
  - Van Slingerland, Peter (Box 365)
  - Vare, Glenna (Box 366)
  - Veiller, Bayard & Marguerite (Box 366)
    ("Martin Vale")
  - Vermes, Hal G. (Box 366)
  - Viazzi, Alfredo (Box 366)
  - Vickers, Roy (Box 366)
  - Victor, Thomas (Box 366)